Hello everyone, if you also want to know how to
fix Your connection is not private error
on Google Chrome or friends, you
want to know how to fix Your connection is not private
problem, then friends, in today
's video, I am going to guide you 1001% working process to fix Your connection is
not private, attackers might be trying to steal
your information, this is the error that you
get to see on Google Chrome.  I will
guide you through the entire process of fixing it.  Now guys, first of all it is
very important for you to know
why you are facing this problem.  So guys,
you face this problem only when you
open an HTTP website on Google.  So
guys, when you open a website with HTTPS,
you will not face any such problem.
But guys, you will face this problem only when you open a website with HTTP.
Because guys, the
websites which start with HTTP are
third party websites.  Now guys,
here it is important for you to know
how this problem will be fixed?  So
guys, there is a small setting in Chrome browser, you have to
turn it off.  So
guys, your problem will be fixed here.
Now guys, I
will tell you the complete process here to fix the problem.
Now basically something like this happens to you
when you search anything on Google Chrome.  For
example, here I search Google.com on Google Chrome in
front of you.  If
you also
search any website like this then guys from now on you will see that
your connection is not private.  Attackers might be
trying to steal your imagination.  Some such
problem is seen.  So
guys how to fix this problem now
?  For this you have to click on Back to Safety.
Guys, as soon as you click on this, then
you have to come to the home page and
click on the three dots.  Then
after that guys, here you
will see the settings option below.  So you have to
click on the settings option.
After clicking on Settings, guys, here you will
see the option of Privacy and Security.  So you have to click on Privacy and Security.
After clicking on this
you have to scroll.  Now guys here
you will see a safe browsing option at the
top.  So first of all you have to
select it and open it.  So guys,
after clicking on Safe Browsing, here you will have
your enhanced protection.  So you have to
tick No Protection Not Recommended.
After ticking this, you have to
click on turn off here.  Save browsing has to be
turned off.  After this you have to
come back a little.  Now guys, the important setting is
here you will see the option of Always
Use Secure Connections below.  So you
can see this option here.  You have to click on this.
So basically guys, whatever
warnings etc. keep coming here, they
come to you from here.  Here you can see
Warn You From Insecure Public Site.
Guys, when you open insecure public sites like
HDT or HTTP sites, then guys, this is where
you face this problem.  So you have to
turn off this setting.
You have to turn off the setting Always Use Secure Connections.
Guys, as soon as you
turn off this setting and come back and search anything on Google,
you will not face that error.
As you can see here, I have
searched Google.com for example.
So here you can see that Google has opened.
And the problem we had has been
easily fixed here.  So guys
here was a little setting that you have to
turn off inside Google Chrome.   With this
you can fix the Your Connection Is Not Private
problem very easily.
Now guys, many
people face the problem of This site can't be reached on Google Chrome.
If you
want to learn how to fix it, you
can watch this video by clicking here.